女子の監督を務められました
三上真二さんでした。
今日のこのゲーム
解説はシドニーオリンピック
いけないということです。
対戦ということですから
なんとか勝っていかなきゃ
２０１２ロンドンパラリンピック
をお伝えしました
（クロンダイク）
ここまで　当財団が行ってきた
事業を　ご覧いただいてきました。
You've all seen what our organization has accomplished.
私どもが目指すものは　ただ一つ。
人類の　さらなる進化です。
We have only one goal in mind:
progress the evolution of mankind.
人間は　その秘めたる可能性を
いまだ　開花させてはいません。
The immense possibilities hidden within us have yet to be released.
サナギから　チョウへと羽化したとき→
When we break out of our chrysalises like butterflies,
戦争もなく　貧困もなく
差別もなく　国境もない→
we will be free of war, poverty, discrimination, and borders.
そんな理想の世界を
必ず実現できるはずです。
Such a utopia is within realization.
その輝かしい未来のために
私どもは努力を惜しみません。
For the sake of building this bright future, we will spare no effort.
私は　皆さんに　お約束しましょう。
I hereby promise all of you,
レーベンヘルツ財団が　この地上に
楽園を建設することを！
the Lebenherz Foundation shall create paradise on Earth!
lost te saguri de sagashiteta
Lost, trying to find it blindly with my hands.
tozasareta mirai no kotae nante doko ni mo nai
But the key to the locked future is nowhere to be found.
hashiru shoudou ima kaidoku funou
Undecipherable urges surging.
found kudaketa hazu no unmei wo
I found the fate I believed broken.
mijukuna yume no naka de kikoetekitan da
I heard it in my immature dream.
saigo made I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you till the very end.
tachitomaranai kono hari dake wa
I can't stop. I hear nothing else.
boku no asu wo kizamu oto tsukisasu
How this needle carves my future.
shinjitsu kara nigetara ima
I'm running away from the truth now.
genjitsu ni mo maketara ima
I'm losing to reality now.
nani ga nokoru no (nokoru no)
What will be left?
kazoekirenai kono kizu dake ga
The countless scars on my body
boku no kinou wo zanzou toshite kataru
are the only thing telling the story of my past.
unmei ga hodokete mo ima
Even if fate falls apart now,
sonzai wo kowashite mo ima
even if existence shatters now,
boku no michi wo yuku yo
I'm walking down my own path.
It's now or never.
This is what they say: "Live your life today."
There will always be, there will always be a way.
Lord of the Board
（ホイスト）お見事な演説でした。
クロンダイク様。
That was an extraordinary speech, Lord Klondike.
彼らには　あの程度の戯れ言が
お似合いだ。
I simply gave them the foolish prattle that they like to hear.
（メランコリィ）ねえ　おじさま　何か
面白いことはありませんの？
Say, isn't there something fun to do around here?
オルペウス・オーダーの仲間ごっこも
終わって　私　退屈～。
I'm so bored now that the Orpheus Order act is over.
（ホイスト）申し訳ございません。
フリーセルの行方は　いまだ　つかめず。
I'm very sorry, but Freecell's whereabouts are still unknown.
（クロンダイク）気にすることはない。
Worry not.
（メランコリィ）あら。
（ホイスト）これは…　フリーセル！
Ah!
Is that... Freecell?
クロンダイク様が　彼を？
Lord Klondike, did you...
誰であろうと　私の計算から
逃れることなど許されない。
No man is allowed to defy my calculations.
（ホイスト）それでは　すでに。
Does that mean that the time has come?
According to the latest data sent from his ring,
彼のリングから抽出した　最後の
データにより　ファイナル・リングは完成した。
the Final Ring is now complete.
全ては　私の計算どおりに
動いている。
Everything is going according to my calculations.
はい。
（クロンダイク）メランコリィ　支度をしなさい。
Indeed.
Melancholy, get ready.
Are we going somewhere fun?
どこか　遊びに行きますの？
ああ　儀式を始めにね。
Yes. The ceremony is about to begin.
（ギャモン）…ったく　ダウトとピノクルのやつ
どこ消えちまったんだ？
Cripes, where've Doubt and Pinochle gone off to now?
（ノノハ）せっかく　ＰＯＧが
保護してくれたのに…。
The POG went through the trouble of looking after them,
何も言わずに
居なくなっちゃうなんて。
yet they vanished without even saying anything...
Those guys sure know how to piss me off.
どこまでも
気に入らねえやつらだぜ。
（アナ）
アナが思うに　ギャモン　寂しそう！
I think... you just miss them!
さっ　寂しくなんかねえし！
でも　ミゼルカたちは救えたし→
Why would I miss them ?!
But now that we saved Mizerka and the others,
オルペウス・オーダーとの戦いは　こっちが
優勢ってことで　いいんだよね？
haven't we pretty much won the fight against the Orpheus Order?
（キュービック）いや　やつらの組織の
全貎は未知数だし　なにより…。
No, we're still not sure about their actual numbers,
and most importantly...
（カイト）クロンダイク。
（３人）あっ。
Klondike.
フリーセルたちに　レプリカ・リングを付けて
操っていた　全ての黒幕→
He gave Freecell and the others their replica rings
and has been pulling all the strings in the background.
そいつの顔が
さっぱり　見えてこねえ。
I still have no idea who he is.
ダウトたちも　素性は知らねえって
言ってたしな。
Even Doubt and the other guys said they don't know him.
クロンダイク　一体　何者なんだ？
Who could this Klondike guy possibly be?
（警報音）
あっ！？
何！？
（フンガ）これは　緊急隔壁が
勝手に閉じていく！
All the emergency firewalls are closing.
（メイズ）外部とも　完全に交信不能！
All outgoing communications have been cut off.
何だ　あれ？　一体　何が
起こったんだ！？…　うっ！？
What? What's going on?
（メランコリィ　モニター音）「うっふ。
カ～イトさん　遊びましょっ」。
Ka-i-to! Let's play!
アハハハッ！
お前ら　どういうつもりだ！
What the hell are you doing?
今度は　ＰＯＧに
ケンカでも売ろうってのか！？
You wanna have a go with the POG this time?
あら
勘違いなさらないでくださる？
Oh, don't get me wrong.
これくらいのこと　その気になれば
いつだって　できましたのよ。
We could've easily done this anytime we wanted.
それが　たまたま
今日になっただけですわ。
うっ。
It just happened to be today.
メランコリィ様のいたずらが
過ぎたようで申し訳ございません。
I apologize for Lady Melancholy's pranks.
本日は　オルペウス・オーダーの指導者
クロンダイク様のメッセージを→
We're here today to deliver a message from the leader of the Orpheus Order, Lord Klondike.
お持ちいたしました。
クロンダイクだって！？
From Klondike?
（クロンダイク　モニター音）
「やあ　大門カイト君。　私がクロンダイクだ」。
Hi there, Daimon Kaito. I am Klondike.
（一同）あっ！
「君をゲームに招待したい」。
I want to invite you to a game.
ゲーム？
「君も　そろそろ→
A game?
I'm sure you want to meet with me by now.
私に会いたくなっているのでは
ないかね。→
ならば　正々堂々　戦って
決着をつけようではないか。→
Let's have a fair match and end this once and for all.
君の大好きなパズルで…」。
With a puzzle you love so dearly.
ふざけやがって！
そうよ！　そんな…。
That son of a bitch!
Yeah, who would—
"Who would ever go along with that request?"
「そんな身勝手な要求は
（一同）うっ。
のめるはずがない」。
「君たちは　そう思っている。→
Is that what you're all thinking?
しかし　当のカイト君の心は
揺らいでいるのではないかな？」。
However, Kaito's heart still wavers.
うっ。
「では　最後の一押しと　いこう。→
So let me give you one last push.
フリーセル君は　現在
私の手のうちにある」。
Freecell is in my hands now.
何！？
「リングから解放し→
What?!
Do you not wish to save him from the ring?
救ってやりたいのではないかね
彼を…」。
ぐっ！
「信じる　信じないは君の自由だ。→
It's up to you whether you believe me or not.
君とのゲームに　ふさわしい舞台を
用意しているよ」。
A fitting stage for the game is ready when you are.
うふっ…。
ご案内いたします。
I shall lead the way.
Are you really sure about this?
ねえ　ホントに大丈夫なの？
罠かもしれないのに…。
It might be a trap!
しかたないよ。　フリーセルが
捕まってるって言うんだから。
Do we have a choice?
He said he has Freecell!
That could be a lie too!
それだって
ウソかもしれないじゃん。
アナが思うに　ウソでも本当でも
関係ない。
えっ！？
I think... it doesn't matter if it's a lie.
あんなこと言われて　あのバカが
黙ってられると思うか？
Do you think this moron could sit still after hearing all that?
クロンダイクの野郎
なかなかの策士だぜ。
This Klondike guy is one hell of a player.
何が待っていようと
心の声
受けとめて　勝ってやるさ。
Whatever's waiting for me, I'll deal with it and win!
（ギャモン）
一体　どこまで連れてかれるんだ？
Just where are they taking us?
あっ　あれ！
あぁ？
Look!
これは…。
Is that it?
（クロンダイク　スピーカー）「遠路はるばる
ご苦労だったね　大門カイト君」。
Thank you for coming all this way, Daimon Kaito.
クロンダイク！　フリーセルは　どこに居る！？
Klondike! Where's Freecell?!
それは　君が　私に勝利したときに
教えてあげよう。
I'll tell you if you can defeat me.
（ギャモン）ふざけやがって！
何様のつもりだ！
Kiss my ass! Who do you think you are?
貴様らこそ　誰に向かって
口をきいている。
And who are you to talk back to me like that?
You still don't get it?
「まだ　分からないのか？　私は
君たちに施してやっているのだ。→
I'm doing you a favor.
本来　存在するはずもない
私とのゲームの機会を」。
Normally, you'd never even get the chance to play a game with me.
いやっ。
上がってきたまえ。
Come on up. I'll play with you.
相手になってやろう。
（ギャモン）クロンダイクの野郎
今さら　何だって→
What could've happened to make Klondike wanna play face-to-face?
差しで　やり合う気になったんだ？
じゃあ　何か　別の目的が？
Maybe he has some hidden intentions?
アナが思うに　あの人は真っ暗。
何も見えない。
I think... he's pitch black. I can't see anything.
I'll find out who he really is!
僕が探ってやる…　やつの正体を！
（メランコリィ）さあ　おじさま
楽しませていただきますわ。
I'll have fun watching this game!
うふっ。
あんた　分かってるの？
Don't you get it?
あんただって　あのクロンダイクとか
いうやつに　操られてるのよ！
He's just playing with you too!
いい？　ミゼルカやダウトたちのリングは…。
アハハハハッ　ハハハッ。
Listen! The rings of Mizerka and Doubt...
You're the one who doesn't get it.
分かってないのは
あなたの方ですわ。
私は　あいつらとは
違うんですもの。
I'm different from them.
えっ！？
ほら　始まりますわよ。
あっ。
Look, it's beginning.
（ホイスト　スピーカー）「このゲームは
対戦型迷路パズル『迷走フィールド』」。
This is a duel maze, the Maze Field.
Both players draw their own maze on the 20x20 field.
まずは　２０×２０のフィールドに
迷路を描いていただきます。
ただし　相手に
迷路の壁は見えません。
However, a player cannot see what the other is drawing.
その見えない迷路を　互いに解く…
それが　このゲームの目的です。
They both must solve an invisible maze.
That is the goal of this game.
両者とも　今　相手がいる地点を
ゴールとした迷路を作成して下さい。
You must make mazes with the opponent's position as the goal.
心の声
作って解く…
ギヴァー　ソルヴァー→
Draw and solve.
Giver and Solver abilities are both tested in this puzzle.
心の声
両方の能力が試される
パズルってわけか。
心の声
戦いは　すでに始まってる！
The fight has already begun.
（クロンダイク）しかし　つくづく
愚かだったな。　ダウト君たちは。
Doubt and the others are so naive.
ああ？
最後まで信じていたのだろう？
They believed up until the last moment, didn't they?
全ての人間に分け与えるために
リングを開発しているのだと。
That we're developing the ring for all mankind.
全て…　ウソだよ。
It's all a lie.
What?!
何っ！？
そんな…。
じゃあ　どうして！
But...
Then why?
（クロンダイク）
理想を掲げておけば　愚か者たちは
いくらでも利用できる。
If I raise the banner of a utopia, fools will come to serve me willingly.
真の目的は　他でもない。
There is only one reason:
私のための　ただ一つの
ファイナル・リングを作ることだ。
I'll make a single Final Ring just for myself.
ファイナル・リング！？
A Final Ring?!
全ては　私の計算どおりに
動いてくれた。
Everything has moved according to my calculations.
フリーセル君も…　そして
大門カイト君　君もだ。
Freecell and you as well... Daimon Kaito.
I kept experimenting all around the world to complete the ring.
リングの完成のため　私は　世界中で
実験を繰り返してきた。
だが　君ほど　よいデータを提供して
くれる素材は　存在しなかったよ。
But I've never seen something that could provide as much data as you.
くっ…。
（ギャモン）てめえ　ふざけんじゃねえ！
Who do you think you're screwin' with?!
そうよ！　人を何だと思ってるの！
Yeah! What are peoples' lives to you?!
お前なんかのために　フリーセルたちは
運命を狂わされたのかよ！
Freecell's... no, everyone's fates were twisted for your own convenience?!
（クロンダイク）感謝しているよ。
I'm very grateful.
許せねえ…。　これ以上　てめえの
思いどおりには絶対にさせねえ！
You'll pay for this.
I won't let you have your way anymore!
（ホイスト）
迷路の準備が整ったようですね。
先攻は　カイト様です。
The maze is complete. Sir Kaito has the first move.
Shall we begin?
（クロンダイク）それでは　始めようか。
（クロンダイク）覚醒の儀式を。
The ceremony of awakening!
あの人も　レプリカ・リングを！？
He's wearing a replica ring too?
（メランコリィ）あら　おじさまのリングは
ただのレプリカじゃなくってよ。
His ring isn't just any replica.
あれこそが　ファイナル・リングですわ！
That's the Final Ring itself!
（ホイスト）それでは「迷走フィールド」　プレー！
Maze Field, play.
いくぜ！
Let's do it!
The players move in turns.
（ホイスト）プレーヤーは　交互に
フィールドを進むことができます。
（ぶつかる音）
ぐわ～！　あぁ。
（ホイスト）壁に衝突した時点で停止し
相手の手番となります。
A player's turn ends when he hits a wall, then the next player's turn starts.
そして　先にゴールにたどりついた
プレーヤーの勝利です。
The player who makes it to the goal first wins.
心の声
ただ　試行錯誤を繰り返しても
ゴールには　たどりつけねえ。
I can't make it to the goal using trial and error.
相手の作った迷路を
心の声
読み取って　全体を推理する。
I'll have to figure out the puzzle he's made and predict everything.
心の声
こいつは　とてつもなく
高度なパズルだぜ！
This is one hell of a difficult puzzle!
うわっ！
フン…。
（ぶつかる音）
フム。
えいっ。
（ギャモン）苦戦してるな　カイト。
そんな…。
Kaito's having a hard time.
But...
It's no surprise.
（キュービック）
無理ないよ。　何のヒントも無いのに
見えない壁をよけて　進むなんて。
He has to map out and solve a maze he can't even see, without any hints.
相手の思考を　とことん読み取る
とてつもない能力が必要なんだ。
It requires a perfect understanding of the opponent's thoughts.
I see. So this is your puzzle.
なるほど。　これが　君の迷路か。
どうなってる？
心の声
やつの迷路が　さっぱり見えねえ！
What's going on?
I can't figure out his maze at all.
心の声
おまけに　この迷路からは
心が　何も感じられねえ。
I can't even feel his heart in this puzzle!
何なんだ？
心の声
この　のっぺらぼうな迷路は！
What's up with this maze of nothingness?
（クロンダイク）
初めに言っておくべきだったな。
君は　私には決して勝てない。
I should've said this beforehand, but you can't win.
Huh?
あっ！？
「それが　私の計算の答えだ」。
That's the result of my calculations.
黙ってろ！
計算どおりの反応だ。
Shut your mouth!
That answer was in my calculations as well.
計算　計算　うっせえんだよ！
うわっ！
You can go wipe your ass with your calculations!
これが　パズルか…
他愛もない遊技にすぎんな。
So this is a puzzle?
A plain little game, nothing more.
何だと！？
失敬。
What?!
Pardon me.
実際に　パズルに興じるのは
今日が初めてなものでね。
This is the first time I've ever attempted a puzzle.
For me, this is merely a tool to reach my goal.
私にとって　このパズルは　目的を
達成するための手段にすぎない。
そう。　君や　フリーセル君たちと同じ
ただの道具だよ。
Merely a tool, just like you and Freecell.
じゃあ　あの人は
パズルの素人ってこと？
Does that mean he's a newbie to puzzles?
そんな人が　どうして
カイトよりも早く…。
Then how can he be faster than Kaito?
まさか！　これが　完成された
ファイナル・リングってやつの力なのかよ！
It must be the power of the completed Final Ring.
（キュービック）違う！
これは　リングの力なんかじゃない！
No... This isn't the ring's power.
あいつのリングは
まだ発動していない！
His ring hasn't activated yet.
What?
Klondike's fighting with his own power.
（キュービック）クロンダイクは　あいつ自身の
力のみで戦っている！
That's impossible!
（ギャモン）そんなバカな…。
あいつは　すでに　カイトを
凌駕してるっていうのかよ！
So he's just that much better than Kaito?
（アナ）アナが思うに
そんな人のリングが動き出したら…。
I think... if such a person used the ring...
We'd be in trouble.
（ギャモン）マジで　ヤバいぜ…。
But then what's the point of this game?
だとしたら　このゲームの意味って
一体　何なんだ？
アハハハハハッ！
いいざまですわ　大門カイト。
Look at you now, Daimon Kaito!
おじさま　もっと
いじめてやってちょうだい。
Give him hell, Old-man Klondike!
うっせえぞ　上からメラ子。
Quit makin' a racket, Mela-chick!
パチモン・リング付けられた
パチモン野郎は　黙ってやがれ！
A poser girl with a fake ring should just keep her trap shut!
言ったはずですわよ…　私は
他のやつらとは違うんだって！
I told you, I'm different from them!
What? What the heck?
なっ！　何なんだ　これは！？
どうしたの？　キューちゃん。
What's up, Cubie?
分かったんだ！　以前　戦った時の
データと　今のリングの反応。
I got it! The data from the earlier fight and the signal of this ring...
あいつのは
レプリカ・リングじゃなくて…。
Hers isn't a replica ring!
お分かりいただけまして？
私が本物だってことが。
Do you understand now? My ring is the real thing.
本物って？
A real one?
I believe "pearls before swine" is the appropriate phrase.
宝の持ち腐れとは
まさに　このことだな。
どういうことだよ！？
What's going on here?!
Lady Melancholy is wearing a real Orpheus ring.
（ホイスト）メランコリィ様が　お付けになって
いるのは　本物のオルペウス・リング…。
そして　メランコリィ様は
真のファイ・ブレインの子供なのです。
She is also a true child of the Phi Brain.
（ホイスト）かつて　クロンダイク様は
オルペウス・オーダーに保管されていた→
Long ago, Lord Klondike placed his hands on the real Orpheus ring being held by the Order.
本物のオルペウス・リングを
手にされました。　しかし…。
However...
（クロンダイク）リングが選んだのは
私ではなく　メランコリィだった…。
The ring chose Melancholy, not me.
だが　メランコリィは　ファイ・ブレインになろう
とする野心さえも→
But Melancholy didn't even try to become a Phi Brain.
持ち合わせていなかった。
All that Phi Brain and Puzzle of God mumbo-jumbo is such a waste of time.
だって　ファイ・ブレインだとか
神のパズルだとか→
面倒くさいんですもの。
私は　楽しく遊べれば
それで　いいんですのよ。
If I can play around and have fun, that's enough for me.
はぁ。　お前　だからレプリカ・リングを…。
So that's why you made the replica rings!
Yes, to earn the power of the Phi Brain.
（クロンダイク）そう。
ファイ・ブレインの力を得るために→
何としても
完成させる必要があったのだ。
I had to complete it, no matter what.
For that purpose, I used the Orpheus Order.
それゆえ　オルペウス・オーダーを
使わせてもらった。
人類解放の大義を利用して
私のための　ただ一つの→
I used the noble goal of helping mankind as my cover
ファイナル・リングを完成させるために。
to complete the one and only Final Ring for myself.
私が求めるもの。
What I want...
What I want is a mind capable of calculating and controlling...
それは　この世界で起きる事象
全てを計算し　動かす頭脳だ。
all events in this world!
私が　ファイ・ブレインとなった暁には→
The moment I become a Phi Brain,
この世界の
ありとあらゆる出来事が→
every single phenomenon of this world will be dancing on the palm of my hand!
私の手のひらの上で
回るようになるだろう。
ざけんな！　神様にでも
なろうっていうのかよ！
Keep dreaming! Do you want a throne in Heaven too?
神？　そんなものの存在を
信じたことは　１度もない。
Heaven? I've never once believed in such a thing.
しかし　その力を手に入れたとき
人々は　私を「神」と呼ぶだろう。
However, after I gain my power,
I'm sure many people will call me God!
んなこと　絶対にさせねえ！
何が計算だ！
I won't let you have your way!
To hell with your calculations!
てめえの計算なんか
ぶち壊してやる！
I'll prove every one of them wrong!
Right here, right now!
俺が　今　ここで！
大門カイト君。
私の計算どおり…　君の負けだ。
Daimon Kaito, just as I calculated,
you lose.
ふざけやがって…。
俺に解けないパズルは　ねえ～！
You bastard!
There's no puzzle I can't solve!
心の声
この迷路は　何かが　おかしい。
Something's weird about this puzzle.
If I were to connect all the walls I've hit so far,
今まで　ぶつかった壁が
心の声
全部つながってるとすると→
閉じた空間ができて
心の声
迷路として成立しなくなる。
it'd be closed and wouldn't work as a maze.
あっ　まさか！
心の声
Wait a minute...!
I knew it!
やっぱりな！
フフフッ。
心の声
これは　最初っから
迷路なんかじゃねえ。
This was never a maze!
ただ　壁を　バラバラに
心の声
並べてあるだけだ！
He just randomly put walls down!
（ぶつかる音）
読めたぜ　このパズル！
心の声
I understand the puzzle now!
まったく　君は計算どおりだよ。
You act just as I calculated, Daimon Kaito.
大門カイト君。
やったぜ　カイト！
そのまま　ゴールまで行っちゃえ！
Nice job, Kaito!
Go straight for the goal!
Stop!
（アナ）ダメ！
えっ！？
ダメ…。
Stop...
カイト　パズルを解いちゃダメ～！
Kaito, you mustn't solve it!
I saw through it!
見えた　この勝負。
俺の勝ちだ！
I win!
待っていた…　それを！
（リモコンのスイッチを入れる音）
Just what I was waiting for!
何が起こってるの？
分からない。
What's going on?
I don't know!
フィールドが　何かを
増幅しているみたいだ。
The field is amplifying something.
（キュービック）まさか…。
ファイナル・リングが　動き出した！
Don't tell me...
The Final Ring activated!
見える…　見えるぞ。
I can see... I can see it all.
今までの大門カイトのデータから
パズルの答えが…。
Based on Daimon Kaito's data, this puzzle...
これが　リングの力か…。
Is this the power of the ring?
計算どおり　リングの覚醒は成功した。
Just as I calculated, the ring has activated.
おじさま　ついに
なってしまいましたのね…。
Old-man Klondike, you've finally become a Phi Brain.
ファイ・ブレインに。
What the hell have you done?!
お前　一体　何しやがった！？
（ホイスト）
ファイナル・リングの起動は　大門カイト様→
To activate the Final Ring, we needed power of you,
ファイ・ブレインに限りなく近づいた
あなたの力が必要だったのです。
Daimon Kaito — the person infinitely close to the Phi Brain.
このフィールドは　カイト様の力を
増幅させる巨大な装置。
This field is a large machine built to amplify Sir Kaito's power.
その力を起爆剤とし
今　ファイナル・リングは覚醒しました。
Using that power as a trigger, the Final Ring has now activated!
お遊びは　これで終了だ。
The game is over.
感謝するぞ　大門カイト君。
I must thank you, Daimon Kaito.
君なしでは　リングの覚醒は
成されなかった。
I could never have completed the ring without you.
Klondike, you son of a...
クロンダイク…　てめえ…。
さあ　帰ろうか　メランコリィ。
はい　おじさま。
Let's go, Melancholy.
Okay, Old-man Klondike.
待て　クロンダイク！
あっ。
Stop, Klondike!
フリーセルは…　フリーセルは
どこに居るんだ！？
Freecell... Where is he?!
ああ　あれか。
Ah, him?
フリーセル！
Freecell!
（クロンダイク）彼には　リング完成のための
生け贄となってもらった。
He served as a sacrifice to complete the ring.
データ採取の際の衝撃で
意識を失ってしまったがね。
He lost consciousness from the shock of retrieving the data.
フリーセル…　フリーセル～！
Freecell...
Freecell!
（フリーセル）カイト…。
Kaito...
eiyuu kidori itsu datte shinjita muteki no kankaku
I think I'm a hero and believe that I'm invincible.
tatakatte iru no wa chikyuu no tame nanka janai
I'm not fighting for the world.
motto mai peesu de
It's for a more personal,
sou motto shoujikina negai no tame
a more honest wish.
nando to naku kizutsuite mo
No matter how many times I'm hurt